
未来
The future.

是一个黑暗 孤寂的世界
A dark, desolate world.

充满战争 苦难 和损失...
A world of war, suffering, loss...

双方都是如此
on both sides.

无论是变种人 还是敢于帮助他们的人类
Mutants and the humans who dared to help them.

哨兵计划最初是玻利瓦尔·特拉斯克博士提出的设想
The Sentinel program was originally conceived by Doctor Bolivar Trask.

在七十年代初 他是全球顶尖的武器专家
In the early '70s, he was one of the world's leading weapons designers.

但暗地里 他一直在用变种人进行试验...
But, covertly, he had begun experimenting on mutants...

利用他们的特殊能力推进自己的科研
using their gifts to fuel his own research.

在过去的十多年里也没有过相关的安全事件
We haven't had an incident in over 10 years.

这是我们中情局的朋友提供的资料
This was acquired by our friends at the CIA.

这篇论文的作者...
It's a dissertation...

是牛津大学的一个变种人
written by a mutant at Oxford University.

内容如下...
And I quote...

"对尼安德特人来说...
"To Homo Neanderthalensis...

"他们的变种近亲 智人..."
"his mutant cousin, Homo Sapiens..."

也就是人类...
which is us...

"是畸形的
"was an aberration.

"变种的智人一旦出现...
"The arrival of the mutated human species, Homo Sapiens...

"较他们来说处于进化劣势的近亲 马上走向了灭亡
"was followed by the immediate extinction of their less evolved kin."

现在 我们成了尼安德特人
Now, we are the Neanderthal.

你说的是你自己吧 特拉斯克博士
Speak for yourself, Dr. Trask.

如果这一次你们仍然低估了敌人...
You do that with this enemy...

带来的就不再是遥远国度的土地之争了
and it won't be some border skirmish halfway around the world.

起立!
Atten-hut!

稍息
At ease.

他们去停机坪那边了
They were headed towards the tarmac.

瞧你 我猜你是大器晚成吧
Look at you. I guess you're a late bloomer.

看你骨瘦如柴的 力气倒不小
You're pretty strong for a scrawny kid.

从那该死的吊灯上下来 汉克
Get off the bloody chandelier, Hank.

你是个敏锐的人
You're a perceptive one.

好吧 你激起了我的兴趣 你想怎样?
All right, you've piqued my interest. What do you want?

答对了 就像我说的 你很敏锐
Top marks. Like I said, you are perceptive.

越南战争恶化了
the war in Vietnam got worse.

许多老师...
Many of the teachers...

还有大一点的学生 都被征兵了
and older students were drafted.

帮我打印一下行程好吗?
Would you mind typing up my itinerary?

让你这个盗窃癖有机会闯进五角大楼去
You, you kleptomaniac, get to break into the Pentagon.

因为这座建筑是种族隔离时期建的 所以他们...
The building was constructed during segregation, so they...

争夺占领日本帝国的硫磺岛
fought for and captured the island of Iwo Jima from the Japanese Empire.

抓着你的脖子 防止你扭伤
I'm holding your neck so you don't get whiplash.

什么?
What?

扭 伤
Whiplash.

可能我刚说的时候你没有听清楚...
Perhaps you didn't hear me when first I spoke...

但是你必须明白...
but it is imperative that you understand...

这一层已全面封锁 你们必须转移至第三层...
we're in a complete lockdown situation. We have to get you to the third floor...

我在驾驶舱见到了飞行计划表 你们去巴黎干嘛?
I saw your flight plan in the cockpit. Why are you going to Paris?

来自世界各国的外交官已于今日陆续抵达皇家宾馆
The diplomats from all around the world are arriving here today at the Hotel Royal.

这是个历史性的日子
It's an historic day.

宣告着美国武装力量正式撤离越南
It's the official ending of the United States' military involvement in Vietnam.

这位是南越南共和国的外交部长...
There we have the South Vietnamese Foreign Minister...

以及其他几位南越的政要
with other South Vietnamese dignitaries.

我们有一个新的敌人
There is a new enemy out there.

这个敌人 枪弹杀不死...
An enemy that will render your arsenals useless...

军队打不赢...
your armies powerless...

诸位的国家将无法抵抗
and your nations defenseless.

这场战役中 你们需要一种全新的武器 我称它为哨兵机器人
You will need a new weapon for this war. I call them Sentinels.

以古时候守卫城邦大门的勇士们命名
Named after the ancient guardians that stood at the gates of the citadel.

他们拥有鹞式战斗机的飞行能力
They have the aeronautic capabilities of a Harrier jet.

装备的机枪每分钟能发射...
Armed with guns that can fire off...

超过2000发热敏陶瓷子弹
more than 2,000 rounds per minute of thermo ceramic ammunition.

拥有了这个武器 我们将不会伤及无辜
With this weapon, there will be no human collateral damage.

你被人下了迷药
You're on acid.

有人给你下了强效迷幻药 明白吗?
Somebody gave you really bad acid, yeah?

昨天 巴黎和平首脑会议...
Yesterday, the Paris Peace Summit...

被不明攻击者的出现打断...
was rocked by the appearance of unidentified assailants...

这种生物的外貌前所未见
the likes of which the world has never seen.

举国上下陷入持续的恐慌 人们纷纷追问...
Mass hysteria has gripped the nation as people ask...

"他们从哪儿来? 他们是否还会回来?"
"Where did they come from? Will they be back?"

而最重要的问题是 "他们是敌是友?"
And most importantly, "Are they friend or foe?"

哪怕让我看到螺丝钉动一下 我也会把这玩意儿插入你的喉咙
If I see so much as a screw move, I will jam this into your throat.

他们能在巴黎街上刮下来的只有这些了
That's all they were able to scrape off the pavement in Paris.

我认为变种人是我们的救赎
I see mutants as our salvation.

一个共同的敌人
A common enemy.

我们将共同奋斗 抵抗终极敌人
A common struggle against the ultimate enemy.

种族灭绝
Extinction.

我相信我们的新朋友...
I believe our new friends...

会帮助我们进入新的时代 比尔
are going to help us usher in a new era, Bill.

一个真正长久的...
A new era of genuine...

和平时代
and long-lasting peace.

那么 这就是我们的未来
So this is what becomes of us.

艾瑞克是对的
Erik was right.

人类害我们沦落至此
Humanity does this to us.

除非我们能为他们指引更好的道路
Not if we show them a better path.

你还相信这些?
You still believe?

就因为人们犯了错 迷了路...
Just because someone stumbles, loses their way...

并不意味着他们会永远迷失方向
it doesn't mean they're lost forever.

有时候我们都需要一点帮助
Sometimes we all need a little help.

我不是之前的我了
I'm not the man I was.

一旦展开思想...
I open my mind...

那些声音几乎要把我吞没
and it almost overwhelms me.

你害怕了 脑波增幅器知道这点
You're afraid, and Cerebro knows it.

所有那些声音...
All those voices...

是如此痛苦
so much pain.

你害怕的不是他们的痛苦
It's not their pain you're afraid of.

而是你的 查尔斯
It's yours, Charles.

虽然令人恐惧...
And as frightening as it may be...

但痛苦会让你更强大
that pain will make you stronger.

如果你允许自己去感受它...
If you allow yourself to feel it...

拥抱它...
embrace it...

它会令你变得超乎想象的强大
it will make you more powerful than you ever imagined.

这是我们最强大的天赋...
It's the greatest gift we have...

承受他人的痛苦 从不屈服
to bear their pain without breaking.

它源于...
And it's born...

人类最伟大的力量
from the most human power.

希望
Hope.

拜托了 查尔斯...
Please, Charles...

我们需要你重拾希望
we need you to hope again.

你们畏惧我们是对的
you are right to fear us.

我们才是未来
We are the future.

我们才是继承这个星球的人
We are the ones who will inherit this earth.

任何阻挡我们的人...
And anyone who stands in our way...

都会遭受和你们眼前这些人...
will suffer the same fate as these men...

一样的命运
you see before you.

今天原本是你们展示能力的日子
Today was meant to be a display of your power.

相反 我要让你们看看...
Instead I give you a glimpse...

我们种族能对你们造成怎样的毁灭
of the devastation my race can unleash upon yours.

把这个当做对世界的警告吧
Let this be a warning to the world.

柏克明斯特·富勒就是一位典型的...
Buckminster Fuller is a great example of an architect...

怀有类似乌托邦理念的伟大建筑师
whose ideas were very similar to those of a utopian future.

数不清的选择决定着我们的命运
Countless choices define our fate.

每一个选择 每一个瞬间...
Each choice, each moment...

都在时间的长河里掀起涟漪
a ripple in the river of time.

你要我们怎么处理他 史崔克上校?
What do you want us to do with him, Major Stryker?

足够的涟漪...
Enough ripples...

就能够翻转浪潮
and you change the tide.

把他交给我吧
I'll take him from here.

因为未来从不曾有定数
For the future is never truly set.
